top10cloudstorage.com 2013-05-17

# Cloud Storage Reviewed. - Infomation on the Best Cloud Storage Providers

### Privacy Policy

**Your Privacy is Important**

The protection of your privacy is of the utmost concern to us.  We make every attempt to protect your private information and hereby present this decree of that commitment.  This document explains how we gather information and what we do with it.  Because of the importance of this document, we have made it readily available to any visitor and user of our website.  Should you ever have any questions regarding our policies regarding your privacy, please feel free to return to this page.  You may also access this document via link at any point where your identifiable personal information may be needed.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google advertising initiatives, namely Google Adsense, uses a system that requires the use of cookies.  This site uses the aforementioned advertising.  Google, a third party vendor of advertising on this website utilizes DART cookies to better serve their advertisers, customers and visitors to this website and other sites across the internet.

Should you ever wish to deny Google the ability to use cookies, please know that you may visit their website <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.  This link will also give you more in-depth information regarding Google’s policies regarding DART cookies and their network privacy policy.  The tracking of the aforementioned cookies are solely instruments of Google and fall under their privacy policies.

Additional third party advertising networks and advertising servers may also utilize cookie tracking to follow the activities of users on this website.  This information is used to determine its overall effectiveness of their advertising concerns.  Other third party advertising vendors have their own policies regarding network privacy and user privacy. [cloudstoragefinder.com/ ](http://www.cloudstoragefinder.com/) neither controls nor has access to the cookies that these vendors may use.

**Our Commitment to the Privacy of Children**

[cloudstoragefinder.com/ cloudstoragefinder.com](http://www.cloudstoragefinder.com/) does not and will not gather information from individuals that we know are under the age of 18.  This website is in no way designed to attract the interests of individuals under the age of 18.

Our Terms of Service does not permit individuals under the age of 18 to access our service.

**Personal Information Collection**

Visiting [cloudstoragefinder.com/ cloudstoragefinder.com](http://www.cloudstoragefinder.com/) will enter the visitor’s IP into a general log that holds time and date of the visitor’s access of the site.  This is general information used only to determine trends in visitations, help in the administration of the website and also offer insight into a visitor’s navigation of the site to provide broad information pertaining to demographics used only for internal purposes.  IP information is not directly linked to any identifiable information regarding the visitor.

**Linking to Third Party Websites**

As a service to the visitors of [cloudstoragefinder.com/ cloudstoragefinder.com](http://www.cloudstoragefinder.com/), this website offers links to other websites for the purpose of reference for use by our visitors.  [cloudstoragefinder.com/ ](http://www.cloudstoragefinder.com/) is not responsible for the policies regarding privacy on external websites that we link to.  Third party website privacy policies may differ from the one we present here.

**Privacy Statement Changes**

We may alter our policies at our discretion and at any time.  Questions regarding the privacy policy displayed here may be addressed to [support@cloudstoragefinder.com](mailto:support@cloudstoragefinder.com)

**Please view our[Terms of Use](http://www.cloudstoragefinder.com/terms-of-use/) as well as our FTC Disclaimer. **
